Guide to the Willard Dickerman Straight papers, 1825-1925.
Straight, Willard Dickerman papers, 1825-1925.
- Partial Box List
  - Series VI Events After Willard Straight's Death
    - Publications and Drafts
      - Notes (Box 25, Folder 9)
        For biography: biographical information, lists of places visited and friends, transcription of grades from Bordentown Military Institute and Cornell, list of people to whom copy of biography was sent, outline of events in Willard Straight's life.
      - Biography--miscellaneous chapters. (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
      - Biography--Introduction, Chapter 1. (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Biography--Chapter 2 and 3. (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Biography--Chapter 4. (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Biography--Chapter 5-8. (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Biography--Chapter 10-11. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Biography--Chapters 11, 13, 14. (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Biography--Chapter 13 and 14. (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Biography--miscellaneous chapter revisions. (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Biography reviews--clippings, 1924-1925. (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Transcribed letters of thanks for copies of the biography sent to friends from Dorothy. (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
      - Original letter of thanks for biography from Warwick Greene. (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Artwork Exhibitions (Box 36, Folder 11)
        Programs and cards from exhibitions of Straight's artwork at the Arden Gallery in Manhattan and the Pratt Institute in Brooklyn.
      - Rubaiyat of Omar Khayyam, 1901 (Box 27)
        Given to Willard Straight by Prof. Henry Morse Stephens.
      - Verse and Worse, 1902 (Box 27)
        By John O. P. Bland, illustrated by Willard Straight, published 1902.
      - Willard Straight, 1924 (Box 27)
        By Herbert Croly, published 1924.
      - Portfolio--Some Men of East Asia: From the Original Water-Colors by Willard Straight, published by Asia. (Box 27)
    - Inventories of Straight Household
      - Inventories (Box 26, Folder 8-13)
    - Seances
      - Transcripts (Box 31, Folder 5, 12)
  - Series VII George Collingwood Bennett Papers
    - Correspondence
      - Correspondence, 1903-1917 (Box 39, Folder 1)
        Concerns activities before Bennett came to America with some mention of the Straights and military service.
      - Correspondence, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 2)
        Includes two notes from Bennett to Straight, and mentions military service and returen to America following World War I.
      - Correspondence, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 3-4)
      - Correspondence, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
      - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 10-11)
        Concerns Willard Straight biography, distribution of copies, plans for Willard Straight Hall, list of objects in cornerstone of Willard Straight Hall.
      - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 40, Folder 1)
        Two letters from friends of Straight to Herbert Croly praising the biography.
      - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 6-7)
        Mentions his photography work and contains condolences on death of Herbert Croly.
      - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
      - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
        Includes mention of Bennett's marriage.
      - Correspondence, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
      - Correspondence, 1937 (Box 41, Folder 6-7)
        Mentions reunion of Willard Straight A.E.F. Association, coronation of King George VI.
      - Correspondence, 1938 (Box 41, Folder 8-9)
        Includes mention of Willard Straight A.E.F. Association.
      - Correspondence, 1939 (Box 41, Folder 10-11)
      - Correspondence, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 12-13)
      - Correspondence, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
      - Correspondence, 1943 (Box 42, Folder 5-6)
      - Correspondence, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 7-8)
      - Correspondence, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 9-11)
        Includes correspondence with servicemen.
      - Correspondence, 1946 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
      - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 43, Folder 3-4)
      - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 6)
        Includes Foster M. Coffin of Cornell University on tentative plans for 25th anniversary of Willard Straight Hall; Charles Vevier on the use of the Straight papers for his thesis research; Louis D. Froelick, Henry P. Fletcher, and George D. Marvin on Vevier's research.
      - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 7-8)
        Includes Charles Vevier, George Marvin, and Louis Froelick; cataloging of Straight's Chinese Art; 25th anniversary of Willard Straight Hall celebration.
      - Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 43, Folder 9-10)
        Describes display of Straight's photos for annual meeting of Willard Straight A.E.F. Association; and 25th anniversary of Willard Straight Hall, including writings reflecting on the event, notes, postcards, programs, and list of photos exhibited.
      - Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 11)
        A-Breed
      - Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 12)
        Bridger-Gach
      - Correspondence (Box 43, Folder 13)
        Gilmore-Jackson
      - Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 1)
        Jeffries-McKinley
      - Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 2)
        McNally-Preston
      - Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 3)
        Rennick-Tordis
      - Correspondence (Box 44, Folder 4)
        Turner-unidentified
      - Undated letters and notes of Bennett (Box 44, Folder 5-7)
        Excerpts and transcripts of letters, lists of Bennett's possessions, notes.
      - Recollections of World War II Years at Dartington Hall (Box 44, Folder 8)
        Transcripts of letters to Bennett from servicemen who spent furlough time at Stepping Stones (Bennett's home) during the war in appreciation of hospitality and memory of good times.
      - Guestbook (Box 44, Folder 9)
        Servicemen who visited Bennett during World War II
      - Postcards (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Calling cards (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Personal Records--notes, account notebooks (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Personal Records--notes, photos (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Family records--documents, memorabilia, financial records., 1882-1896 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - Notebooks--notes, addresses, financial records. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Memorabilia and Photographs
      - Memorabilia (Box 45, Folder 2)
        Pamphlets, passenger lists, and miscellany.
      - Australian postcards. (Box 45, Folder 3-4)
      - Straight-Elmhirst family (Box 45, Folder 5-6)
        Correspondence, drawings, cards.
      - Straight-Elmhirst family (Box 45, Folder 7)
        Photos
      - Straight-Elmhirst family (Box 45, Folder 8)
        Children's drawings.
      - Dartington Hall (Box 45, Folder 1)
        Pamphlets
      - Dartington Hall (Box 45, Folder 2)
        Cards, notes, souvenirs, programs from exhibitions of Mark Tobey's artwork.
      - Dartington Hall (Box 45, Folder 3)
        Map, miscellaneous writings, "News of the Day."
      - Dartington Hall (Box 45, Folder 4)
        "News of the Day"
      - Dartington Hall (Box 45, Folder 5)
        Notes of photography and films.
      - Dartington Hall (Box 45, Folder 6)
        Foundation Day guestbook.
      - Dartington Hall (Box 45, Folder 7)
        Certificate from English-speaking Union.
      - Financial Records, 1932-1934 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Financial Records, 1933 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Brochures--on Dartington Hall (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Newspaper Clippings (Box 45, Folder 11)
        About Dartington Hall, World War I, photography, and personal interests.
      - Book made by Bennett in book-binding class at Dartington Hall. (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Book made at book-binding class at Dartington Hall (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Wartime Souvenirs--book cover, patches. (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - World War I Souvenirs--comic books, currency. (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - George Bennett photographs (Box 47)
  - Series VIII Willard Straight Post of American Legion Records
    - Record books, 1937-1945 (Box 48)
      Four volumes including meeting notices, correspondence, and financial records.
    - Record books, 1926-1949 (Box 49)
      Two volumes including meeting notices, correspondence, clippings, and financial records.
- Visual Materials
  - American Cemetery, Suresnes
    - American Cemetery, Suresnes 1919 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - American Expeditionary Forces 1919 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Bilowski, Suresnes, France 1919 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Cemeteries 1919 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Cemetery Beautification 1919 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Ceremonies 1919 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - France, Suresnes 1919 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - World War I 1919 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Cemetery Beautification, Suresnes
    - American Cemetery, Suresnes 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - American Expeditionary Forces 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Doughboy (Statue) 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Sculpture 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Vizzavona, Paris, France 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - World War I 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - France, Suresnes 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Cemetery Beautification, Suresnes (annotated in French)
    - American Cemetery, Suresnes 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - American Expeditionary Forces 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Cemeteries 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Cemetery Beautification 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Ceremonies 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Doughboy (Statue) 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - France, Suresnes 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Levasseur, Paris, France 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Loizeau, Paris, France 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Sculpture 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Tree Transplanting 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Vizzavona, Paris, France 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - World War I 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Student Scrapbook
    - Cornell U. 1897-1901 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Cornell Widow 1899-1901 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Cornellian 1899-1901 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Delta Tau Delta, Beta Omicron Chapter 1899-1901 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - New York, Ithaca 1899-1901 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Savage Club 1899-1901 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Social Life 1899-1901 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Sports 1899-1901 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1899-1901 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Cornell Era 1897-1901 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Cornell U. 1897-1901 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Cornell Widow 1897-1901 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - New York, Ithaca 1897-1901 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Social Life 1897-1901 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Sports 1897-1901 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1897-1901 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Consul General, Mukden (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Groups 1907 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Railroads 1907 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1907 c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Arnell, Charles J. 1907 c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Landscapes 1907c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Mezger, Otto 1907c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Russia, Siberia 1907c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Transporation, Sailboats 1907c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Railroads 1907c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Trans-Siberian Railroad 1907c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Consulate, Mukden 1907c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Consul General, Mukden (autographed)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1907c. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Panoramic Views of China
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Camel Caravans n.d. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - China n.d. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Camel Caravans n.d. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Diplomatic Career Residences (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - China, Peking 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Egan, Martin 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Japan, Kyoto 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Korea, Seoul 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Macarthur, Douglas 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Morgan, Edwin V. 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Paddock, Gordon 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Portraits 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Residence, Mukden 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Residence, Peking 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Residence, Seoul 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Roosevelt, Alice L. 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Consulate, Mukden 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Legation, Peking 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Legation, Seoul 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Architecture, Interior 1905-1909 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Peking Photographs (note by George D. Marvin)
    - Railroads 1910 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Residence, Peking 1910 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1910 c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Architecture, Interior 1910 c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - China, Nanking 1910c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - China, Peking 1910c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Gatrell, Thomas J. 1910c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Kalgan Railway 1910c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Landscapes 1910c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1910c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Railroads 1910c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Legation, Peking 1910c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Walls 1910c. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War
    - Japanese Army, Infantry 1905c. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War
    - Russo-Japanese War 1905c. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Friends and Associates
    - Calhoun, William J. 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Camp of Intruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Casenave, Maurice 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - China, Manchuria 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - China, Peking 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Cecil 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Richard 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Fletcher, Henry P. 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - French, Charles 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Gatrell, Thomas J. 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Morgan, Edwin V. 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - New York, Plattsburg 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Paddock, Gordon 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Portraits 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Tsai, T'Ing-Kan 1902-1915 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Willard Straight's Career
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - China, Manchuria 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Richard 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Egan, Martin 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Gatrell, Thomas J. 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Korea 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Morgan, Edwin V. 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - New York, Plattsburg 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Portraits 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1901-1915 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Camp of Instruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York (annotated)
    - Camp of Intruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York 1915 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Harris & Ewing, Washington, D.C. 1915 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Preparedness Movement 1915 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore 1915 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Army 1915 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - William J. Fallon, Woodhaven, New York 1915 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - World War I 1915 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Country Houses and House Parties
    - Architecture, Exterior 1912-1915 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Casenave, Maurice 1912-1915 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - England 1912-1915 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - New York, Westbury 1912-1915 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1912-1915 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Social Life 1912-1915 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Views of China
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Chinese 1907 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Priests 1907 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Boats 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Camel Caravans 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Ceremonies 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - China, Manchuria 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Rural Scenes 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Street Scenes 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Transporation, Sailboats 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Camel Caravans 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Horsecarts 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Sedan Chairs 1907c. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Russo-Japanese War, Japan, China, and Korea (annotated)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Bridges 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Ceremonies 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Children 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - China, Manchuria 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Crime and Punishment 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Cecil 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Richard 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Dress 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Egan, Martin 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Fletcher, Henry P. 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Griscom, Lloyd 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Japanese Army, Officers 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Korea, Seoul 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - MacDonald, Claude 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Manshu Maru (Ship) 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Morgan, Edwin V. 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Occupations 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Palmer, Frederick 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Port Arthur 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Portraits 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Railroads 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Railroads, Construction 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Russo-Japanese War 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Ships 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Street Scenes 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Transporation, Oxcarts 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Battleships 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Railroads 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Streetcars 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Wendell, Barret 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Japan, Tokyo 1905-1909 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Women 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Russian Navy 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1904-1905 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Group Portraits (mounted)
    - Palmer, Frederick 1904-1911 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Russo-Japanese War (annotated)
    - Russian Navy 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Alnu 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Architecture, Exterior 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - China, Manchuria, Mukden 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - China, Peking 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Dalny 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Dress 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Japan 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Japan, Hakodate 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Japanese Army, Infantry 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Japanese Army, Officers 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Japanese Navy, Salvage Operation 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Port Arthur 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Portraits 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Railroads 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Red Cross 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Russo-Japanese War 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Ships 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Hospital Ships 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, Railroads 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Railroads 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - China, Manchuria 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Dalny 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Army, Artillery 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Army, Infantry 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Japanese Army, Officers 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Korea 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Palmer, Frederick 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Pershing, John J. 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Railroads, Construction 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Red Cross 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Russo-Japanese War 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Sculpture 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Ships 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Battleships 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Hospital Ships 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Transportation, Railroads 1904-1905 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Peking in Ruins
    - German Army 1912 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China (annotated)
    - Portraits 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China (annotated)
    - Powkee, Shanghai and Nanking, China 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Architecture, Interior 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Ceylon, Colombo 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - China, Nanking 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - China, Peking 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Chinese Army, Infantry 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs Service 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Egypt, Port Said 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Empress Dowager, Tz'u His 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - German Army, Infantry 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Landscapes 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Ming Tombs 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Monasteries 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Russo-Japanese War 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Ships 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Straight, Willard D. 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Suez Canal 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Temples 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career
    - Tz'U His 1901-1909 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Voyage to China, Chinese Imperial Maritime Customs School, Early Career